tvweb.com 2013-10-31

# Privacy Policy

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC, Inc. has created this privacy statement to describe our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: "Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com" at [http://www.tvweb.com](http://www.tvweb.com/).  We seek to protect your private information so that you have a pleasurable viewing experience on our Web site. We will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. Please return to this page from time to time, as we will be updating this statement as our services continue to grow. We welcome and encourage questions, comments, and suggestions. Please contact us at [webmaster@tvweb.com](mailto:webmaster@tvweb.com) with any questions.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies store information about your use of a particular Web site or service and are typically used to make services more convenient and personalized. Most cookies are "session cookies," which are automatically deleted whenever you leave a Web site, although some cookies remain on your computer until you remove them.

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser(s) (i.e. Gorilla Nation, MTVN, Brightroll, Adconion, Google, Tribal Fusion, Husky Media Advertising.com, DoubleClick and/or others) may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

## How We Use Cookies

We use cookies

  * (1) to estimate the number of visitors to our Web site
  * (2) to measure general traffic patterns, and 
  * (3) to personalize information and services we provide to you on the site.

Companies that place ads on the Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com Web site — including, but not limited to Gorilla Nation, MTVN, Brightroll, Adconion, Google, Tribal Fusion, Husky Media Advertising.com, DoubleClick and/or others — may also use their own cookies to help determine the frequency and placement of particular ads. Your browser controls how cookies are used and can be set to not allow them. However, it is possible that some parts of the Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com site may not function properly if your browser refuses our cookies.

We may, from time to time, use cookies to store your zip code and email address for use with certain current or future services such as e-mail update list(s), showtimes e-mail services, local showtimes profiles, theater and movie preference profiles.

## Cookie Notification and Disabling

Most browsers permit you to set the browser to accept, reject, or notify you of cookie use. However, some parts of the Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com Web site may not function properly if your browser is set to reject cookies.

## Personally Identifiable Information

**What Personally Identifiable Information Is**

Personally identifiable information is your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information.

## Where We Collect Personally Identifiable Information

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com collects personally identifiable information when you (1) subscribe to our mailing list(s), (2) enter contests, (3) buy products, make referrals, or use the "tell a friend" option, and (4) submit feedback, questions, or "contact us" messages.

## How We Use Personally Identifiable Information

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com uses your personally identifiable information to personalize your experience on our Web site, to deliver products and/or services ordered and/or purchased by you and to contact you. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com also compiles aggregate data from all of our customers to prepare internal reports about which pages are popular, how many total unique users visit our site, and different traffic patterns. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com does not combine your personally identifiable information with information about pages visited, purchases made, or any other click-stream data.

## Who We Disclose Personally Identifiable Information To

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com may disclose some personal information to outside companies who help Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com with the administration and delivery of newsletters, promotional games, trivia contests, and sweepstakes. For example, a company who administers a sweepstakes for us may use your e-mail address to update you on your status in the sweepstakes. Or, our newsletters may be distributed by another company that will use your e-mail or shipping address for delivery. The Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com Web site contains links to other Web sites. Although we do not provide any personally identifiable information to these companies, we cannot guarantee your privacy once you leave the Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com Web site. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of Web sites with links on our site. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com or others.

## Communication

We collect personally identifiable information such as first and last name and email address when you sign up for our email list(s). These email services provide Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com users free opt-in updates about the Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com site and movie information and/or content. We may also request secondary information, such as your movie preferences, which we will use to help personalize the site for you in the future. We may also on occasion send promotional and informational mail to you from Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com. You may opt-out of receiving these secondary communications by sending an email with "remove" in the subject line to [webmaster@tvweb.com](mailto:webmaster@tvweb.com).

## Demographic Information

Demographic information may be collected on the web site. The information will only be shared with any third-parties in an aggregate format.

## Public Forums

This site makes voting and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal opinion. Personally identifiable information is not made available to the public or to other users and voting is anonymous. However, when using message boards, your user name and email address – which constitutes personally identifiable information, provided by you, is made available on the message boards.

## Log Files

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com, both using its own systems and the systems of others (such as Google or Quantcast, among others) automatically logs information such as IP addresses, ISPs, and browser type but does not link that information to personally identifying information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

## Sharing of Information

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com is engaged in "powered by" relationships as more fully described herein. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com does not share any personally identifiable information with third-parties, other than its partners as herein described, and will otherwise only share information in aggregate form. We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies from banner ads are collected by advertising networks, and we do not have access to this information.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Specifically, this site uses the services of a variety of advertisers, rep firms and networks, including but not limited to: Gorilla Nation, MTVN, Brightroll, Adconion, Google, Tribal Fusion, Husky Media, DoubleClick and/or other various independent advertisers and/or networks for serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages when you visit our Web site. More particularly, the third-party advertising technology that we and our advertising partners use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize certain of our our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," of the use of such Web beacons used by ad providers utilizing Doubleclick/Boomerang, please [click here.](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx)

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Employees are notified in staff meetings of security policies and practices regularly. Access to data limited and employees obtain access to log files by a secured password. Pipeline Media Labs, LLC periodically reviews web security and ensures that all policies and practices are adhered to within the company.

## Children

**Our Policy For Guests Under Age 18** Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com is committed to protecting the privacy of children. We encourage parents and guardians to explore the Internet with their children. Visitors under age 18 should not submit any personally identifiable information to Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com.

## Links

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are ‘clicking’ to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

## Correct/Update or Cancel Subscription

Users can change their information with Pipeline Media Labs, LLC.com by emailing a request to [webmaster@tvweb.com](mailto:webmaster@tvweb.com). If you wish to unsubscribe from any Pipeline Media Labs, LLC mailing list, please email [webmaster@tvweb.com](mailto:webmaster@tvweb.com) using the e-mail address you would like removed and type “UNSUBSCRIBE” as the subject of the message.

## Notification of Changes

Pipeline Media Labs, LLC privacy practices may change periodically. TVweb.com will notify users of changes only if the information collected from the user differs from that stated at the time of collection. TVweb.com may also obtain the user’s consent by posting notice on the site.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact: TVweb Email: [webmaster@tvweb.com](mailto:webmaster@tvweb.com)
